karachisnob.com 2011-02-05

# Karachi Snob.com Privacy Policy

At KarachiSnob.com, we respect the privacy of our users and know the importance of concealing and protecting their information.

We may collect information that can identify you ("personal information"), such as your name and email address, when you or other users provide it to us while using our website or in some other manner, either from other KarachiSnob owned projects, from our business partners, and/or from other third parties.

We also may collect other types of information in the following ways when you visit our website:

  * Our server logs automatically collect information, such as your IP address, your browser type and language, location, and the date and time of your visit, which helps us track users' movements around our site and understand trends. 
  * We may assign your computer one or more "cookies" which may collect information to facilitate access to our website and to personalize your online experience.
  * We may use standard Internet tools which collect information that tracks your use of our website and enables us to customize our services and customer experience.

**Information Others May Collect**

We allow third-party companies to display their information on our websites. However, we do not provide any personal information to these companies.

If you post information about yourself or others, or communicate with others using our website, please note that we cannot control who reads your postings or what they do with the information you provide. We encourage you to use caution when posting personal information.

**How We May Use Information We Collect**

We may use information to:

  * Fulfill your requests for products and services
  * Send our newsletter or other related mailings
  * Facilitate use of our website
  * Analyze and improve our website, products and services
  * Identify and protect against fraudulent and other misuses of our website
  * Enforce our Terms of Use

**Your Choices  **

You may choose:

  * Not to provide personal information, although that may result in your inability to obtain certain services or use certain features of our website.
  * To stop receiving promotional emails or newsletters from us by sending an email to the contact address at the bottom the newsletter or this policy.
  * To delete or decline cookies changing your browser settings, although if you do so, some of the features or services of our website may not function properly.
  * To review and update your personal information by contacting us at the email address below. 

**Security  **

We take appropriate physical, electronic, and other security measures to help safeguard personal information from unauthorized access, alteration and/or disclosure.

**Changes To Our Privacy Policy**

We may occasionally update our Privacy Policy to reflect changes in our practices and services. If we make changes in the way we collect, use, or share your personal information, we will notify you by sending you an email to the email address you most recently provided to us and/or by posting notice of the changes on our website.

** How To Contact Us **

If you have any questions about this summary, our Privacy Policy or our information practices, please contact us by e-mail or postal mail:

KarachiSnob.com  
P.O. Box 3402  
Karachi, Pakistan. 74800   
**[info@karachisnob.com  
](mailto:info@karachisnob.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy%20at%20KarachiSnob.com) **
